http://www.hexazen.com/privacy

Menu
This privacy policy sets out how hexaZen uses and protects any information that you give hexaZen when you use this website.hexaZen is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.hexaZen may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 1, 2009.Information We CollectWe may collect the following information:NameContact information including email addressDemographic information such as preferences and interestsOther information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWhat We Do with the Information We CollectWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:We may use the information to improve our products and services.From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable administrative, technical, and physical procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.If you have a password, help protect it by keeping your password confidential. If you share a computer, especially a public computer, terminate your Internet session by logging out and closing the browser to guard against subsequent users having access to your information.Links to Other WebsitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling Your Personal InformationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposesIf you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at contact @ hexazen.comWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Privacy    Copyright
